<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubernetes Development Framework (KDF) on KDF</title>
    <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kubernetes Development Framework (KDF) on KDF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kdf.csco.cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/explore-kubernetes-main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/explore-kubernetes-main/</guid>
      <description>Open up a SOCKS connection by connecting to your KDK kdk ssh  Install Firefox We prefer Firefox because it allows one to manage network proxy configurations independently of the host operating system.
Download Firefox here or install it through a prior-installed package manager as prior steps have used.
Configure your web browser to connect via the KDK SOCKS proxy It may be beneficial to start Firefox with the profile manager so that you can keep these settings separate from the default instance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/explore-kubernetes-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/explore-kubernetes-note/</guid>
      <description>In this section, explore your newly provisioned Kubernetes cluster along with all of the basic services you have deployed via the framework-deploy code repository. You will connect to the admin panels of the services you have deployed. Connecting to these admin panels requires a web browser which is configured to use the KDK as a SOCKS proxy. The KDK will proxy all web requests to the internal ingress, so that one may access the dashboards using the configured cluster DNS name (*.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-main/</guid>
      <description>(inside your KDK container)
Clone the framework-deploy repo using git. #### Run this command if you have configured your GitHub account for public key SSH. git clone git@github.com:cisco-sso/framework-deploy.git #### (OR) Run this command if you have not configured GitHub for public key SSH. git clone https://github.com/cisco-sso/framework-deploy.git  Get your ~/kube/config into the KDK TODO(jmdots): Fill in this section
This will copy your kube config into the KDK and modify the docker-for-desktop configuration context to work from within your kdk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-note/</guid>
      <description>Framework-deploy is a git repo which implments the KDF deployment pattern. The boilerplate structure in framework-deploy is made to fit perfectly with the tools available in the KDK container.
Create a private fork of framework-deploy and use it to hold non-secret Kubernetes-related application configuration files and templates. In the KDF pattern, templates and configuration files for tools like mh are hosted in a private fork of framework-deploy. mh allows you to template and deploy Helm Chart values overrides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-install-maclinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-install-maclinux/</guid>
      <description> Install the Kubernetes Development Kit (KDK). curl -sSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cisco-sso/kdk/master/files/install | bash  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-install-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-install-windows/</guid>
      <description> Install Prerequisites # Windows Powershell as Administrator choco install openssh  Install the Kubernetes Development Kit (KDK). # Windows Powershell - NOT AS ADMINSTRATOR Set-ExecutionPolicy Bypass -Scope Process -Force iex ((New-Object System.Net.WebClient).DownloadString(&#39;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cisco-sso/kdk/master/files/install.ps1&#39;))  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-note/</guid>
      <description>The KDK CLI creates a Docker container with many tools already installed and ready for you to develop with Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-usage/</guid>
      <description> Print KDK usage information. kdk  Configure KDK. When running kdk init, please accept when prompted
Please respond affirmatively when prompted for:
 Keybase directory mounting Enabling the SOCKS proxy at default port 8000  kdk init  Run the KDK container and log into it. kdk ssh  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/keybase-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/keybase-note/</guid>
      <description>Keybase makes sharing secrets with your team much easier. A Keybase user may be added to one or more Keybase Teams, at which point the team&amp;rsquo;s secret files are accessible under your local filesystem at [[ MOUNTPOINT ]]. Scripts and automation may then locate secrets within the Keybase filesystem at common paths.
Later in this guide (upon kdk init), the kdk command will ask to mount the host&amp;rsquo;s Keybase filesytem to the KDK container at /keybase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/post-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/post-install/</guid>
      <description>(optional)
Add your public SSH key to source control systems. This is optional if you are using ssh-agent, which the KDK automatically forwards. Otherwise, you may directly configure the pre-generated ssh key which is used to connect to the KDK, within each source control provider.
Add content of ssh public key ~/.kdk/ssh/id_rsa.pub
 To your Github Account Keys To your Bitbucket Server https://&amp;lt;BITBUCKET-SERVER&amp;gt;/bitbucket/plugins/servlet/ssh/account/keys  Customing your .bash_profile If you have installed Keybase, you may customize your bash profile by creating the file /keybase/private/&amp;lt;user-keybase-id&amp;gt;/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backlog</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/backlog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/backlog/</guid>
      <description>Roadmap Priorities  Dockerized KDK Multi-cluster DRY Configuration  e.g. How to manage highly redundant umbrella charts or mh configs across many kubernetes clusters. Next generation of mh technology, could be something else  Kubernetes Individual Identity (Security)  OIDC Provider Integration  Kubernetes RBAC (Security) Kubernetes Audit logging (Security) Multi-tenant Kubernetes Clusters  Per-region Kubernetes clusters Individual Namespaces per project.  Service Mesh  East/West (intra-cluster)  e.g. pod in one cluster can talk to service in another cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deployment Packages</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/deployment-packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/deployment-packages/</guid>
      <description>Deployment Packages (Helm Charts) (components list)
All changes to deployment packages were upstreamed.
How to generate parts of this doc: git checkout git@github.com:cisco-sso/framework-deploy.git cd framework-deploy/apps ls | awk -F&#39;-&#39; &#39;{OFS=&#34;-&#34;;NF--;print &#34;- &#34; $0;}&#39;|sort | uniq   cassandra cert-manager cert-manager-configs chaoskube cluster-autoscaler consul docker-registry drone elasticsearch elasticsearch-curator elasticsearch-exporter envoy external-dns filebeat filebeat-elasticsearch grafana hackmd kafka kafka-manager kafka-rest kafka-schema-registry kibana logstash metallb metrics-server minio mysql nginx-ingress nginx-reverse-proxy oauth2-proxy openebs prometheus raw redis redis-ha stolon ureplicator vault  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started &gt; Linux</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/linux/</guid>
      <description>Linux is not currently supported.
However, the Mac instructions may help you get KDF running on Linux.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started &gt; Mac</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/mac/</guid>
      <description>Requirements  macOS High Sierra (10.13) or later is required. You must execute all commands as an administrative (sudo-allowed) user. 8 GB RAM 2 CPU cores  Step 1: Homebrew Open a Terminal.  Spotlight Search ( Command[⌘] + Space[&amp;quot; &amp;quot;] ) -&amp;gt; Terminal  Install Homebrew. /usr/bin/ruby -e &amp;quot;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Homebrew/install/master/install)&amp;quot;  Step 2: Docker Install Docker for Mac. brew cask install docker  Start Docker.  Spotlight Search ( Command[⌘] + Space[&amp;quot; &amp;quot;] ) -&amp;gt; Docker -&amp;gt; ( Enter)   At the Are you sure you want to open it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started &gt; Windows</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/windows/</guid>
      <description>Requirements  Windows 10 Pro or Windows 10 Enterprise is required. You must execute all PowerShell commands as an administrative user. 8 GB RAM 2 CPU cores BIOS Settings with Hardware Virtualization Enabled (VTx and VT-d)  Step 1: Chocolatey Open a Powershell terminal as Administrator.  Windows Search -&amp;gt; Windows PowerShell -&amp;gt; right click Run as Administrator  Install Chocolatey. # Windows Powershell as Administrator Set-ExecutionPolicy Bypass -Scope Process -Force iex ((New-Object System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/kubernetes/</guid>
      <description> Testing Chaoskube Litmus Test Delete all nodes
Helm Chart Practices Selecting a Helm Chart Helm Chart Code Review Cluster Deployments Local Machine AWS Vsphere Openstack </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Training Resources</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/training/</guid>
      <description> Docker  Getting Started:  https://docs.docker.com/get-started/   Kubernetes  A Comic-Book Intro to Kubernetes  https://cloud.google.com/kubernetes-engine/kubernetes-comic/  Official Kubernetes Tutorials  https://kubernetes.io/docs/tutorials/  Kubernetes Concepts  https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/   Helm  Quickstart  https://docs.helm.sh/using_helm/#quickstart   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patterns</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/patterns/</guid>
      <description> Development Environment Framework-Deploy Custom Chart Repository Monitoring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/team/</guid>
      <description> Agreements Code Reviews Upstreaming People </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/tools/</guid>
      <description> Keybase Kubernetes Development Kit kdk (components list: autogen)
framework-deploy mh </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>