<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting-starteds on KDF</title>
    <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting-starteds on KDF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-main/</guid>
      <description>(inside your KDK container)
Clone the framework-deploy repo using git. #### Run this command if you have configured your GitHub account for public key SSH. git clone git@github.com:cisco-sso/framework-deploy.git #### (OR) Run this command if you have not configured GitHub for public key SSH. git clone https://github.com/cisco-sso/framework-deploy.git  Change to the framework-deploy directory and take a look around. cd framework-deploy/ ls -a  You should see:
. .. .envrc .git .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/framework-deploy-note/</guid>
      <description>Framework Deploy AKA framework-deploy is a boilerplate git repo in the KDF deployment pattern. The boilerplate structure in framework-deploy is made to fit perfectly with the tools available in the KDK container.
Create a private fork of framework-deploy and use it to hold non-secret Kubernetes-related application configuration files and templates. In the KDF pattern, templates and configuration files for tools like mh are hosted in a private fork of framework-deploy. mh allows you to template and deploy Helm Chart values overrides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-install/</guid>
      <description> Install the Kubernetes Development Kit (KDK). curl -sSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/cisco-sso/kdk/master/files/install | bash  Print KDK usage information. kdk  Configure KDK. kdk init  Run the KDK container and log into it. kdk ssh  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/kdk-note/</guid>
      <description>The KDK CLI creates a Docker container with many tools already installed and ready for you to develop with Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/keybase-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/keybase-note/</guid>
      <description>Keybase makes sharing secrets with your team much easier. A Keybase user may be added to one or more Keybase Teams, at which point the team&amp;rsquo;s secret files are accessible under your local filesystem at [[ MOUNTPOINT ]]. Scripts and automation may then locate secrets within the Keybase filesystem at common paths.
Later in this guide (upon kdk init), the kdk command will ask to mount the host&amp;rsquo;s Keybase filesytem to the KDK container at /keybase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/post-install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/readfiles/post-install/</guid>
      <description> (optional)
Add your public SSH key to source control systems. This is optional if you are using ssh-agent, which the KDK automatically forwards. Otherwise, you may directly configure the pre-generated ssh key which is used to connect to the KDK, within each source control provider.
Add content of ssh public key ~/.kdk/ssh/id_rsa.pub
 To your Github Account Keys To your Bitbucket Server https:///bitbucket/plugins/servlet/ssh/account/keys  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started &gt; Linux</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/linux/</guid>
      <description>Linux is not currently supported.
However, the Mac instructions may help you get KDF running on Linux.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started &gt; Mac</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/mac/</guid>
      <description>Requirements  macOS High Sierra (10.13) or later is required. You must execute all commands as an administrative (sudo-allowed) user. 8 GB RAM 2 CPU cores  Step 1: Homebrew Open a Terminal.  Spotlight Search ( Command[⌘] + Space[&amp;quot; &amp;quot;] ) -&amp;gt; Terminal  Install Homebrew. /usr/bin/ruby -e &amp;quot;$(curl -fsSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Homebrew/install/master/install)&amp;quot;  Step 2: Docker Install Docker for Mac. brew cask install docker  Start Docker.  Spotlight Search ( Command[⌘] + Space[&amp;quot; &amp;quot;] ) -&amp;gt; Docker -&amp;gt; ( Enter)  At the Are you sure you want to open it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started &gt; Windows</title>
      <link>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kdf.csco.cloud/getting-started/windows/</guid>
      <description>Requirements  Windows 10 Pro or Windows 10 Enterprise is required. You must execute all PowerShell commands as an administrative user. 8 GB RAM 2 CPU cores  Step 1: Chocolatey Open a Powershell terminal as Administrator.  Windows Search -&amp;gt; Windows PowerShell -&amp;gt; right click Run as Administrator  Install Chocolatey. Set-ExecutionPolicy Bypass -Scope Process -Force iex ((New-Object System.Net.WebClient).DownloadString(&#39;https://chocolatey.org/install.ps1&#39;))  Step 2: Utilities Install git, curl and sudo. choco install -y git curl sudo  Open Git Bash  Windows Search -&amp;gt; Git Bash  Step 3: Docker Install Docker for Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>